techclap.com 2014-05-21

# Privacy | TechClap.com

At "TechClap.com" [www.techclap.com](http://www.techclap.com/), the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by TechClap.com and how it is used.

**How** **TechClap.com** **Collect User’s Personal Information?**

**Log Files**  
Like many other Web sites, [TechClap.com](http://www.techclap.com/) makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

**Cookies and Web Beacons**  
[TechClap.com](http://www.techclap.com/) does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

**DoubleClick DART Cookie**

  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on [TechClap.com](http://www.techclap.com/)
  * Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to [TechClap.com](http://www.techclap.com/) and other sites on the Internet.
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL – <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html>.

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on [TechClap.com](http://www.techclap.com/) send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

[TechClap.com](http://www.techclap.com/)  has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. [TechClap.com](http://www.techclap.com/) or www.techclap.com privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie" management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites."

**How TechClap.com Use User’s Personal Information?**` **  
**`

  * The email address you provided while subscribing to our newsletter subscription form enables us to send you a daily digest of _TechClap.com_ stories. This subscription is entirely opt-in by the user. (We cannot subscribe you to the newsletter as you personally must have access to the email account in order to verify the subscription.) Subscribers can opt-out of our newsletter at any time by clicking the “Unsubscribe” link that is present on every email at the very bottom of the newsletter. Please note that we currently use **Feedburner** for E-mail Newsletter Delivery, Check Feedburner Privacy Policy at: <http://www.feedburner.com/fb/a/privacy>
  * The email address that you use when contacting us with an news tip or via email or our Contact Form will not be used for any reason but for the purposes of responding to your inquiry by Our Staff. We will not sell, rent, or leak any way our user’s personal information to third parties.
  * Email addresses users have provided in comments are not used for any other reason (It will now shown any way to pubic on Website).
  * If you choose to comment on TechClap.com’s stories through Twitter and/or Facebook Connect, we do not get access to your email address nor do we have any access to your personal data or private information.

**Is Sharing Personal Information Online Safe?**

Any information you share on comment section or any other place at TechClap.com, please note that TechClap.com is a public website, we cannot control the actions of our site users, and we advice you to share your personal information to public at your own risk. We encourage you that sharing personal information is personal matter, and be careful when disclosing information on Internet. **  
**

_With Best Regards,_

**Team**[ **TechClap.com**](http://www.techclap.com/)

For Any Query/Question About Privacy: [Contact Us](http://www.techclap.com/contact-us)
